Chat shows are the staple of late night entertainment TV in many countries.
在许多国家，访谈节目是深夜娱乐电视节目的主要内容。
The US has some of the most famous hosts and the shows are syndicated worldwide.
美国有一些非常著名的主持人，而且这些节目在全球范围内被出售播放。
Jon Stewart does comedy; Oprah Winfrey goes for heartfelt conversation.
乔恩・斯图尔特主持喜剧类脱口秀；奥普拉・温弗里则选择真诚的对话访谈。
But what makes a good interview?
但是，如何完成一次好的采访呢？
Is it catching the guest off guard?
是让放下防备的嘉宾措手不及吗？
Will they reveal something more personal - some juicy gossip that will have us chatting away on social media?
他们会透露一些更私人的事情吗——比如一些有趣的八卦，让我们在社交媒体上闲聊个不停？
Larry King is a veteran.
拉里・金是一位资深主持人。
For more than 25 years he's been hosting nightly shows in which he interviews movie stars, politicians and ordinary people, who are thrown into the spotlight.
25年多来，他一直主持夜间节目，在节目中采访电影明星、政治家和普通人，这些人都被置于聚光灯下。
And the secret to getting the best out of an interviewee?
那么，从受访者那里得到最佳采访效果的秘诀是什么呢？
King says: "If you ask good questions and elicit thoughtful answers then you learn more about the person.
金说：“如果你提出好的问题并引出经过深思熟虑的回答，那么你就能更多地了解这个人。
If the interview's hard – if I begin by saying: ‘Why did you do that?' I'd make you defensive.
如果采访很尖锐——比如我一开始就问：‘你为什么要那么做？’我会让你产生防备心理。
That may be thrilling television, but you don't learn a lot."
这也许会是很刺激的电视节目内容，但你不会了解到很多东西。”
King adds that he's learned that the more he draws back, listens to the answers, and cares about the guest the more he gets from the person.
金补充道，他认识到，他越是回避某些话题，倾听回答，并关心嘉宾，他从对方那里得到的东西就越多。
"You make the camera disappear", he says.
他说：“你要让摄像机消失（让嘉宾忘记摄像机的存在）。”
Another thing Larry King does is ask open questions.
拉里・金做的另一件事是提出开放性问题。
He explains: "I don't want a ‘no'.
他解释说：“我不想要一个‘不’的回答。
I don't want a ‘yes'.
我也不想要一个‘是’的回答。
I want a ‘why'.
我想要一个‘为什么’的答案。
So in other words, I want to be a little kind of dumb, I ask ‘‘What do you mean by that?'"
所以换句话说，我要装作有点‘笨’，我会问‘你那么说是什么意思呢？’”
Being amiable, courteous and curious about the person in front of them – maybe that's what makes a good chat show host.
对面前的嘉宾和蔼可亲、彬彬有礼且充满好奇——也许这就是成为一名优秀谈话节目主持人的关键。
Their biggest talent is making the guest feel at ease.
他们最大的才能就是让嘉宾感到自在。
Another famous American host, David Letterman, seems to know it.
另一位著名的美国主持人大卫・莱特曼似乎也明白这一点。
He once said: "I cannot sing, dance or act; what else would I be but a talk show host."
他曾经说过：“我不会唱歌、跳舞或表演；除了做脱口秀主持人，我还能做什么呢。”
Good idea: let others do the singing – just make them relax and they'll tell us everything!
这是个好主意：让别人去唱歌——只要让他们放松下来，他们就会告诉我们所有的事情！